Richard Osenbrock

Granite Falls, WA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Richard-Osenbrock/f55b504368b44dcd

Accomplished and energetic with a solid history of achievement in

Information technology and Manufacturing. Motivated leader with strong organizational and prioritization abilities.

Areas of expertise include machine execution, optimization and Information technology

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead

Hampton lumber - Darrington, WA -

October 2003 to Present

Machine execution, Ensuring lumber is on size, production lead, running equipment

Town Council

Town of darrington - Darrington, WA -

January 2014 to September 2017

Writing and reviewing ordinances, researching grants, grant writing. Ensuring the publics concerns are delt with in a quick and timing manner.

IT

Hampton - Darrington, WA -

January 2004 to July 2017

Networking, wifi setup/installation, hardware, software, troubleshooting, help desk, field technician, Installation.

EDUCATION

Certificate in Information Technology

Ashworth College - Norcross, GA

February 2008

SKILLS

OPTIMIZATION (10+ years), Information Technology (10+ years), Leadership Training (10+ years), Communications (10+ years), Time Management

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

References

Tony

USNR

Controls engineering manager

[...]

Ryan

PLC Tech

[...]

John

Hampton Lumber

Lead

[...]